<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><sst xmlns="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/spreadsheetml/2006/main" count="136" uniqueCount="115"><si><t>Home Page</t></si><si><t>Feedback</t></si><si><t>Instructions</t></si><si><t>Reference</t></si><si><t>Banner</t></si><si><t>The Most Seamless Warranty Management Software</t></si><si><t>Focus the messaging around increasing revenue and reducing cost

Analytics and Dashboard</t></si><si><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><b/><sz val="10.0"/></rPr><t>IMAGE [</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><sz val="10.0"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">Showcasing a Happy Person (English Female). Circle around the person mentioning Delighful Owner, 1-Click Onboarding, Faster Resolution.]. 

Reference - </t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><color rgb="FF1155CC"/><sz val="10.0"/><u/></rPr><t>https://images.ctfassets.net/a7hvy8sclsq6/59QQoq5npPnrGGWkMngJD0/3e6a6e387f81acb14b8cf679fc857c6f/cb_hero_visual_desktop.png</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><sz val="10.0"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">

</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><color rgb="FF1155CC"/><sz val="10.0"/><u/></rPr><t>https://www.chargebee.com/</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><sz val="10.0"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve"> Banner image</t></r></si><si><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><b/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t>Headline:</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">
The Most Seamless Warranty Management Software

</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><b/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t>Animated line (Like myumbrella.ai):</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">
for D2C Brands
for Shopify Merchants
for Retailers
for Manufacturers

Subtitle:

Warranty registration, claims management, and tracking unified in one system. Reduce the cost of every claim, manage warranties with more control, and make the warranty lifecycle a new revenue channel.</t></r></si><si><t>Get A Demo &gt;</t></si><si><t>Rated 4.8 ★ on G2 | 5 ★ on Shopify App Store</t></si><si><t>Logos</t></si><si><t>Trusted by 500+ brands globally</t></si><si><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">New Logos - </t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><color rgb="FF1155CC"/><u/></rPr><t>https://drive.google.com/drive/u/1/folders/1k4sbSMIf_bkh078lx3lfI332UOz2KprX</t></r></si><si><t>Client Logos</t></si><si><t>Platform</t></si><si><t>All-in-One Warranty Management System. Seamless for Your Team. Effortless for Your Customers.</t></si><si><t>Registration, claims, service, protection plans, and analytics no longer need separate tools. Dyrect connects the full warranty lifecycle, from registration to claim resolution and every service record in between.</t></si><si><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">Befor and After Animcation (On page scroll)
Webflow - https://webflow.com/made-in-webflow/website/before-after-animation

Figma File - 
Before - https://www.figma.com/design/TGUG03JYsgf40Vy3AteE8H/Dyrect?node-id=13791-14472&amp;t=Sbo9ucyXGEZ65MLl-1

After - </t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><color rgb="FF1155CC"/><u/></rPr><t>https://www.figma.com/design/TGUG03JYsgf40Vy3AteE8H/Dyrect?node-id=13799-4485&amp;t=Sbo9ucyXGEZ65MLl-1</t></r></si><si><t>Products</t></si><si><t>The Only Warranty Management System Built for the Full Post-Sale Journey</t></si><si><t>Removing this section</t></si><si><t>Most warranty tools solve one part of the problem. Dyrect covers the entire journey, from the moment a product is registered to the day a claim is resolved and every service interaction in between.</t></si><si><t>PRODUCT REGISTRATION &amp; UPSELL</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">CLAIMS AND SERVICE MANAGEMENT
</t></si><si><t>EXTENDED WARRANTIES</t></si><si><t>INSIGHTS AND ANALYTICS</t></si><si><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">Every section will have a tab with miltiple features Ref - </t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><color rgb="FF1155CC"/><u/></rPr><t>https://emeraldkit.webflow.io/</t></r></si><si><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><color theme="1"/><sz val="9.0"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">EXTENDED WARRANTIES
</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><b/><color theme="1"/><sz val="12.0"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">
</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><b/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">Offer Protection Plans Across More Buying Touchpoints. Keep 100% of Revenue In-House
</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">
Don't leave extended warranty revenue to third parties. Dyrect lets brands sell protection plans and extended coverage directly, at the moment customers are most likely to buy, right on the product page or after purchase. 

– Multi-Touchpoint Offers: Place protection plan offers on the product page, at checkout, and after purchase
– Native Ecommerce Integration: Connect natively with Shopify and other ecommerce platforms
– Self-Serve Plan Management: Let customers activate, view, and renew plans through a self-serve portal</t></r></si><si><t>Image</t></si><si><t>1-Click Registration + Upsell</t></si><si><t>- Registration 
- Upsell (Vouchers)</t></si><si><t>Extended Warranties</t></si><si><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">- Sell Extended Warranty inhouse (ref - </t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><color rgb="FF1155CC"/><u/></rPr><t>myumbrella.ai</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/></rPr><t>)</t></r></si><si><t>Claims &amp; Service Management</t></si><si><t>- Self Service Claims Portal
- Tickets Tracking
- Repair/ Replacements
- Shipments
- Payments</t></si><si><t>(amar)

extended warranties features-|</t></si><si><t>4. Insights and Analytics (powerful)</t></si><si><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><color theme="1"/><sz val="9.0"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">Omnichannel Product Registration &amp; Upsell
</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><b/><color theme="1"/><sz val="12.0"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">
</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><b/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">Turn Every Buyer Into a Reachable Customer
</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">
Stop losing customers to marketplaces and offline retail. Dyrect collects first-party data at the point of registration so every buyer becomes a direct contact the team can reach, retain, and sell to again.

- Omnichannel Registration: Omnichannel product registration through QR code, website, and automatic registration for Shopify orders</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><color rgb="FFFF0000"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">
</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">- Digital Warranty: Digital warranty card and self-serve customer portal
- Post-Registration Upsells: Trigger upsell offers at the exact moment a customer completes registration

</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><b/><color rgb="FF0000FF"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">Create Omnichannel Registration &gt; </t></r></si><si><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><color theme="1"/><sz val="9.0"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">CLAIMS AND SERVICE MANAGEMENT

</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><b/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">Every Claim Logged, Assigned, and Resolved With Full Visibility
</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">
Claims arrive from every direction and service work expands with every unresolved request. Dyrect organizes claim intake, validation, assignment, and resolution so teams can handle service requests with clear ownership and complete visibility.

– Serial Number Validation: Serial number validation catches fraudulent and duplicate claims before they are processed
– Smart Ticket Routing: Automatic ticket assignment with priority levels and real-time status tracking
– Service Workflow Tracking: Repair, replacement, shipment, dealer payment, and OEM chargeback tracking in one workflow

</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><b/><color rgb="FF0000FF"/></rPr><t>Streamline your Claims Process &gt;</t></r></si><si><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><b val="0"/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t>INSIGHTS AND ANALYTICS</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><b/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">

</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><b/><color theme="1"/><sz val="14.0"/></rPr><t>Complete Picture of Your Warranty Operation in One Dashboard</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><b/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">
</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><b val="0"/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">
Know exactly where claims are coming from, which products fail most, how fast the team resolves tickets, and where revenue opportunities are being missed. All in one dashboard, updated in real time.

– Warranty Performance Metrics: Track registration rates, claim volumes, and resolution times across every product
– Defect Trend Detection: Identify high-defect products before they become a cost problem
– Revenue Opportunity Insights: Spot upsell opportunities based on warranty expiry and customer activity</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><b/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">

</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><b/><color rgb="FF0000FF"/></rPr><t>Explore Analytics &gt;</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><b/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">          
                
                
                
                
                
                
                </t></r></si><si><t>Whoever Owns the Post-Sale Problem, Dyrect Solves It.</t></si><si><t>Customer Profile</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">No first-party data. Slow claims processing. After-sales service that costs more than it earns. 
These are not separate problems, they are the same broken post-sale operation hitting three different teams. Dyrect's warranty management software fixes the whole thing.
</t></si><si><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><b/><color rgb="FF000000"/><sz val="10.0"/><u/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">Image.
</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><b val="0"/><color rgb="FF000000"/><sz val="10.0"/><u/></rPr><t>User Profile (with name, email, Phone, Sales Channel &amp; more)</t></r></si><si><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><b/><color rgb="FF000000"/><sz val="10.0"/><u/></rPr><t>Image
(</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><b val="0"/><color rgb="FF000000"/><sz val="10.0"/><u/></rPr><t>Ticketing List, assigning to the repairer)</t></r></si><si><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><b/><color rgb="FF000000"/><sz val="10.0"/><u/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">Image.
</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><b val="0"/><color rgb="FF000000"/><sz val="10.0"/><u/></rPr><t>(Dashboard Profit &amp; Loss Image)</t></r></si><si><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">Reference - Hubspot </t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><color rgb="FF1155CC"/><u/></rPr><t>https://www.hubspot.com</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">
</t></r></si><si><t>Marketers</t></si><si><t>After Sales/ Warranty Managers</t></si><si><t>Business Owner</t></si><si><t>You Have Thousands of Buyers You Cannot Reach</t></si><si><t>Your Claims Process Was Not Built to Scale</t></si><si><t>Your After-Sales Operation Costs Money and Earns None</t></si><si><t>Every product sold through Amazon, offline retail, or a distributor is a customer your brand has no record of. No email, no phone number, no purchase history. Dyrect captures first-party data at the point of product registration so every buyer becomes a direct contact you own, regardless of where they purchased.</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Claims come in through email, WhatsApp, and phone calls. Each one gets logged manually, followed up individually, and resolved slowly. Dyrect replaces that with a structured system where every claim is validated against a serial number, assigned to the right person, tracked in real time, and closed without manual chasing.
</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Every warranty claim your team resolves is an expense with no return. Dyrect turns each service interaction into a revenue touchpoint by surfacing extended warranty plans and upsell offers at the right moment, so the same operation that was draining margin starts generating it.
</t></si><si><t>Learn More</t></si><si><t>Everything You Need to Run Warranty Operations, Built In</t></si><si><t>Capabilities</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">No add-ons, no third-party tools stitched together. Every feature needed to run a complete warranty operation comes built into Dyrect.
</t></si><si><t>ICON</t></si><si><t>Digital Warranty Cards</t></si><si><t>Serial Number Validation</t></si><si><t>Custom Forms and Policies</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">

Replace paper cards with digital warranty records linked to the product and purchase details.</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">
Check product authenticity and warranty eligibility before service activity moves ahead.</t></si><si><t>Set up registration fields, claim forms, and warranty rules for different products and categories.</t></si><si><t>Read more &gt;</t></si><si><t>Self-Serve Warranty Portal</t></si><si><t>White-Label</t></si><si><t>Team Workspaces</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">
Give buyers a clear place to view product details, warranty status, and service activity.</t></si><si><t>The registration page, warranty portal, and customer communications all carry the brand's logo, colors, and tone. Customers interact with the brand, not a third-party tool.</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">

Keep claim ownership, notes, assignments, and service actions organized across internal teams.</t></si><si><t>Testimonial</t></si><si><t>Why 100s of brands trust us?</t></si><si><t>1 Indian + Others Non- Indian</t></si><si><t>Testimonials</t></si><si><t>Already on Shopify? Go Live in &lt;30 Minutes.
Dyrect is rated 5★ on the Shopify App Store. Three steps and your entire warranty operation is running automatically, no developer needed.</t></si><si><t>Shopify</t></si><si><t>Step 1</t></si><si><t>Step 2</t></si><si><t>Step 3</t></si><si><t>Step 1 — Install the App
Find Dyrect on the Shopify App Store and install with a single click. No coding, no technical setup, no back and forth with a developer.</t></si><si><t>Step 2 — Sync Your Products
Select which products need warranty registration. Dyrect pulls directly from your Shopify catalog and syncs automatically.</t></si><si><t>Step 3 — Go Live
That's it. From the next fulfilled order, warranties are registered automatically and customers are notified without any manual work from your team.</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Seamlessly Connect With Your Existing Tools 
</t></si><si><t>Integration</t></si><si><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><b/><color theme="1"/><sz val="12.0"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">Dyrect Plugs Into the Tools Your Team Already Uses

</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">No ripping and replacing your existing stack. Dyrect's warranty management system connects with your ecommerce store, marketing tools, and support platform so data flows automatically where it needs to go.

</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><color rgb="FF0000FF"/></rPr><t>View Dyrect Integrations &gt;</t></r></si><si><t>Real Results From Brands Running on Dyrect</t></si><si><t>Stats</t></si><si><t>4 Mn +</t></si><si><t>500+</t></si><si><t>3X</t></si><si><t>500+ Brands</t></si><si><t>4M+ Customers Served</t></si><si><t>Customers Served</t></si><si><t>Brands Running on Dyrect</t></si><si><t>Higher Attach Rate</t></si><si><t>3x higher attach rate</t></si><si><t>Ready to Optimize Your Post-Sale Operation?</t></si><si><t>CTA</t></si><si><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><color rgb="FF000000"/><sz val="10.0"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">Book a demo and </t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><b/><color rgb="FF000000"/><sz val="10.0"/></rPr><t>see how brands running on Dyrect manage the entire warranty lifecycle</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><color rgb="FF000000"/><sz val="10.0"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve"> without switching tools.</t></r></si><si><t>Sign-up for Demo &gt;</t></si><si><t>From the Dyrect Blog</t></si><si><t>Resources</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Guides, case studies, and insights on warranty management, post-sale operations, and building direct customer relationships.
</t></si><si><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">Ref: Stripe. Built for Growth section. </t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><color rgb="FF1155CC"/><u/></rPr><t>https://stripe.com/in</t></r></si><si><t>resources section -- case study, newsletter, blogs, warranty pages</t></si><si><t>Guide</t></si><si><t>Listicle</t></si><si><t>Footer</t></si><si><t>Faqs</t></si><si><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">Frequently Asked Questions

</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><b/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t>1. What is Dyrect warranty management software used for?</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">

Dyrect is a warranty management platform that helps brands handle product registration, warranty claims, service requests, and warranty tracking in one system. Teams can manage the full warranty lifecycle from customer registration through claim resolution. This helps founders and warranty teams reduce manual work while maintaining a clear record of registrations, claims, and service activity.

</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><b/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t>2. Can Dyrect work with Shopify stores?</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">

Yes. Dyrect works with Shopify and can connect with your store to manage product warranty registration and warranty claims linked to Shopify orders. Once the app is installed, products can be synced from your Shopify catalog and warranty registration flows can run automatically for eligible orders.

</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><b/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t>3. How does product warranty registration work in Dyrect?</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">

Dyrect allows customers to register their products through a branded registration page or portal. Registration can happen through a website link or QR code on packaging. During registration, the system collects key customer information such as email, phone number, purchase channel, and location. This helps brands capture first party customer data and maintain a proper warranty database.

</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><b/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t>4. Can Dyrect help manage warranty claims and service requests?</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">

Yes. Dyrect supports warranty claim management through a structured workflow. Claims submitted by customers can be validated using serial numbers and then assigned to the right team member. Warranty teams can track claim status, manage repairs or replacements, and monitor every service interaction in one place.

</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><b/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t>5. Does Dyrect support serial number warranty tracking?</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">

Yes. Dyrect supports serial number based warranty tracking. Each product can be linked to a serial number or unique identifier so the system can verify warranty eligibility during registration and claims. This helps prevent duplicate claims and improves accuracy in warranty service management.

</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><b/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t>6. Can brands sell extended warranties using Dyrect?</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">

Yes. Dyrect can support extended warranty and protection plan offers. Brands can present extended warranty options during the product registration flow or at other post purchase touchpoints. This helps teams create additional revenue opportunities through warranty upsell programs while maintaining control over the customer relationship.

</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><b/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">7. What integrations does Dyrect support?
</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">
Dyrect can integrate with several tools commonly used by ecommerce and support teams. This includes platforms such as Shopify, Zendesk, Zoho Desk, Mailchimp, and Klaviyo. These integrations allow warranty data, customer details, and service activity to sync with existing support and marketing systems.

</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><b/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">8. What kind of businesses usually use Dyrect warranty software?
</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">
Dyrect is commonly used by ecommerce brands, manufacturers, consumer electronics brands, appliance companies, and businesses that sell physical products with warranties. It helps founders, operations leaders, warranty managers, and support teams manage warranty registration, claims processing, and post purchase customer service more efficiently.

</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><b/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t>9. Does Dyrect support warranty management for brands with dealer and OEM networks?</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">

Yes. Dyrect handles chargeback management from dealers and OEMs directly within the platform. Brands can track which claims originated from which channel and streamline the reimbursement process without manual reconciliation.

</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><b/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t>10. What plans does Dyrect offer?</t></r><r><rPr><rFont val="IBM Plex Sans"/><color theme="1"/></rPr><t xml:space="preserve">

Dyrect offers flexible plans based on the features required, integration needs, and the scale of the warranty operation. Pricing can vary depending on registration volume, claims management workflows, and integration requirements. To learn more about plans or see how Dyrect fits your workflow, you can contact the Dyrect team or schedule a demo

</t></r></si></sst>